

Personal

Name Aapo Soukkio

Address

33310 Tampere

Phone number 0452334618

Email

aapo.soukkio@edu.savonia.fi

Driving licence B, A

Website

https://github.com/AapoSoukkio

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaposoukkio-a132b2244/

Interests

Kitaran soitto / Guitar playing Moottoripyöräily / Motorcycling

Languages

Suomi Native
Englanti Advanced

Aapo Soukkio

I'm 24- years old IT-student and former mining equipment mechanic from Tampere, Finland. At the moment my main focus is on the Information technology studies that are ongoing at Savonia university in Kuopio, Finland. Studies are focusing on software development and design also basics of network technologies are included. My strengths are interest of deep understanding of SW-technologies, excellent communication skills and perseverance.

Now I am looking for a place where to take my software developer skills to the next level and gain ground on IT-industry. My passion as a software developer is SW-design and problem solving. Design to get understanding and vision for the project I am working for, problem solving to get instant confident to get towards to the next challenge.

I have a decent understanding of the following languages/techniques: C#, Java, JavaScript, SQL, React, HTML, CSS. I am also familiar with Azure DevOps and Github in terms of version controlling.

As a private life side at summertime motorcycling takes my free time and at wintertime studies takes nearly all of my time.

Work experience

Asentaja / Mechanic Jul 2017 - Nov 2022

Viatech Oy, Pirkkala

Kallionporauslaite mekaanikko / Mining equipment mechanic

Rakennusapulainen / Construction assistant May 2017 - Jun 2017

Click Henkilöstöpalvelut, Valkeakoski

Pienen hetken toimin rakennusapulaisena ammattikoulun jälkeen

Lehdenjakaja / Paperboy Nov 2012 - May 2013

Tampereen Ykkösjakelut Oy, Tampere

Lehdenjakelu työtä.

Education and Qualifications

Insinööri Tietotekniikka / Bachelor of Engineering, Information Jan 2021 - May 2024

Technology

Savonia-ammattikorkeakoulu, Kuopio

Ajoneuvoasentaja / Car Mechanic Aug 2014 - May 2017

Tampereen Ammattiopisto Tredu, Tampere

References

Janne Polakovski Viatech Oy

+358 40 132 9555

janne.polakovski@viatech.fi

Skills

C#

Java

JavaScript

SQL

React

HTML

CSS